Tang Phuoc Quang

https://phuocquang-portfolio.netlify.app/

८ 039 654 6280 **☑** quanggtangg@gmail.com **%** www.linkedin.com/in/phuoc-quang/

SUMMARY

Hi, my name is Quang, a very junior web developer with almost two years of experience.

Familiar with front-end technologies like reactjs and its ecosystem, basic knowledge of backend development using nodejs/express, and its related technologies.

EDUCATION

Cao Thang Technical College	Sep 2018 - Nov 2019
Major: Computer Networking Management.	
Cybersoft Academy	Dec 2019 - Apr 2020

Major: Front end web development.

SKILLS

Programming Language	Javascript (typescript sometime)
Front-end	Reactjs, Redux, Sass, antd, material,
Back-end	Nodejs, Express, Postgresql
Version Control/ Tools	Github, Gitlab, Jira
OS	Linux (Ubuntu).
Languge	English.

CERTIFICATIONS

Cybersoft's Front end development degree.

Apr 2020

WORK EXPERIENCES

Nexon Dev Vina

April 2022 - Now (in probation)

Front end developer

A little about Nexon, this is a game company from Korea, that succeeded with some games like: Mapple Story, FIFA Online 4, and CSO, ...

And Nexon Dev Vina is a new branch of Nexon in Vietnam (separated from Nexon Network Vina).

I joined this company as a front end developer, to develop some in-house projects, and one of them that I'm working on is

Attendance system:

- A simple project that I'm working on with 3 other guys, create a web app for managing the teams when they come, and leave the office, manage their overtime work and a few others stuff relate to HR and accountant

About the **Technologies:**

- We used Reactjs with a bunch of custom, and a few frameworks like Material, Mantine for components, and TailwindCSS for styling
- On the back-end side, we used nodejs, express, and MongoDB to manage, and process all the data.

And the **Problems** we're facing are:

- follow the business logic
- it's just in beta, for the dev team only, but it's gonna scale up for other teams, and almost a hundred users from other departments.

Goalist Co.,Ltd.

July 2021 - Feb 2022

Front end developer

Project: Jopus connecter LP

https://connecter.jopus.net/en/

- A landing page for hiring and introducing an app to connect foreigners and Japanese HR companies.

My works:

- Collaborate with the design team from Japan.
- Maintain and update and implement some new features for the page.
- Responsive for multiple devices

Project: Casting road

https://hr-visual.jp

Description:

- A web app using data from others HR companies to manage, calculate and compare, to visualize how your company doing (compare with other companies).

My works:

- I joined this project as a front-end developer, working with teammate to create new features following the requirements from client, build UI, and sometimes fix or create new api.

Technologies:

- Reactis, Nextis, Typescript, Spring, Mysql.

Project: Hrog

https://hrog.co.jp/

- A landing and a cms page, created for Hrog Co., to show company works, update frequently company status, and projects, ...

My works:

- Mainly working on updating UI and content of showcase, using HTML, CSS, and Go Hugo

Project: Google App Script

- It's actually not a project, it's just some random task I worked on because a lot of data we're using is stored on Google apps, so it's very important to manage, process, and custom them.

My work:

- Custom data, research, implement and custom library, make things auto.

Technologies:

- Google App Script, AWS s3

Savemoney Corporation - the first company of my life

May 2020 - May 2021

Front end developer

Project: Merchant Tool

Description:

- The merchant tool is an admin page for VNPay to manage all the insurance they have sold.

Responsibility:

- Build UI using UmiJs and Ant Design.
- Integration VNPay API, get and manage all the policies
- Calculate data and render dynamically on many charts.

Gain:

- Some knowledge about BA, design UI.
- There are just me and another teammate working on so there are so many problems that need to be solved.

Technologies:

- Javascript, TypeScript, ReactJs, UmiJs, Redux, NodeJS, Express, RESTful, Postgresql

Project: Insurtech

- An insurtech platform, that connects banks and Insurance companies, gives out a solution for selling and buying insurance much easier. Working with trusted partners such as ZaloPay, VNPay, PVI, PTI, ...

My works:

- Build UI to render a large amount of dynamic data.
- Build an end-user application for selling insurance.
- Manage all end-user applications' API, and write the document for partners.
- Maintain, optimize and develop the current system.
- Build API from a web server connect to multiple databases in a microservice system.

Gain:

- I learn a lot of back-end skills from this project.
- Gain knowledge about the insurance and finance industry.
- My teammates, my leader, and my PO always give me chance whenever they can to challenge me with hard requirement tasks, I sometimes failed, but they still give me another chance to prove myself again. They teach me a lot.

Technologies:

- Javascript, TypeScript, ReactJs, UmiJs, Redux, NodeJS, Express, Sequelize, Graphql, Microservice, RESTful, Postgresql

Cybersoft March 2020 - Apr 2020

Student

It was an e-commerce website about selling motorbikes. I built for the final project to graduated Cybersoft. You can take a look here: https://harley-ecommerce.web.app/

Main responsibilities:

- Build web UI using ReactJs, Ant Design and some react's animation library.
- Build some basic functions such as cart, log in and sign up.

Gains

- I gain a lot of ReactJs knowledge from this project, about Class and Functional Component, Redux, middleware, API.

Technologies:

- React, redux.

Thanks for spending your valuable time on my resume, Hope you have a nice day!